Poe Privacy Policy
==================

Poe Privacy Policy
==================

Poe Privacy Policy
==================

Last updated: Jan 22, 2024

This Poe Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes how your personal information is processed when you use Poe, a platform that lets you communicate with bots powered by third party AI model providers. This Privacy Policy applies to activities by Quora, Inc. and its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively “Quora,” “we” or “us”). This Poe Privacy Policy supplements the [Quora Privacy Policy](https://www.quora.com/about/privacy), which is incorporated by reference. Quora Inc. is the data controller of your personal information and is responsible for providing you with this Privacy Policy.

### **Information We Collect, How It Is Used, & The Legal Basis for Processing**

**Account Information.** We collect your email address and phone number to create an account and verify your identity. We also create a user ID for your Poe account. If you are an existing Quora user, your name, Quora-associated email address, profile photo, and Quora user ID will be used to link your Quora account to your Poe account. Depending on your location we may also ask you to provide your date of birth to verify your age. We use this information to communicate with you, troubleshoot issues, and provide updates on the latest Poe features. This processing is necessary to comply with our legal and contractual obligations to you.

**Contact List.** With your consent, Poe may access and periodically sync your phone’s contact list to make it easy for you to find and connect with your friends on Poe. It is in our legitimate business interests to provide you with a customized experience.

**Device Information.** We collect your device type and operating system details for analytics and to troubleshoot product issues. This is so we can comply with our contractual obligations to you.

**Third Party Application Login.** You can log into your Poe account using third party applications (e.g., Google and Apple). When you log in using this method, we collect your name and email address associated with that third party application for authentication and identity verification purposes. This processing is necessary to comply with our contractual obligations to you.

**Subscription Billing Data.** We use a third party service provider to collect and process your billing information when you subscribe to Poe. The information our billing provider collects may include your name, billing address, your credit or debit card details, phone number, and email address. This processing is necessary to comply with our contractual obligations to you.

**Content Creator Payments.** If you are a content creator on Poe we collect and share your email with our third party payment processor to help facilitate payments to you. We also collect and share your tax information, such as your tax ID and address, with our tax service provider. This processing is necessary to comply with our legal and contractual obligations to you.

**Advertising**. We collect information about you when you interact with Poe ads to measure the effectiveness of our ad campaigns. This information includes your IP address, advertising ID, and ad interaction information. We share your hashed email with our ad platform partners for our paid acquisition campaigns. It is in our legitimate business interest to advertise our platform. Where necessary, we will obtain your consent before engaging in this processing.

**User Research.** We may ask you to help us test new features or participate in surveys to help enhance your Poe experience. Your participation is voluntary and the data we collect is anonymized. With your consent, we may use your personal information to communicate with you. It is in our legitimate business interest to improve our platform.

**Interactions with Bots on Poe.** Our third party AI model LLM providers and third party bot developers may receive details about your interactions with bots on Poe (including the contents of your chats) to provide and generally improve their services, which they may process in their legitimate business interests. Your Poe user account information (e.g., username and email) is not shared with our third party AI model providers or developers. Third party developers that create bots on Poe using APIs may view and store your anonymized chats on their servers to train their models. We may use your interactions on Poe to provide you a personalized experience, such as recommending other bots to explore or topics to discuss.

Keep in mind, any information and files you provide to the bots on Poe will be shared with third party AI model providers and developers powering the bots, and there is no need to share sensitive personal information with the bots (e.g., credit card information, social security information, etc.). For more information about the third party AI model providers and bot developers, please see the respective bot profiles and visit the [Poe Privacy Center](https://poe.com/privacy_center).

For more information about our privacy and data protection practices, including how to exercise your privacy rights, please visit the [Quora Privacy Policy](https://www.quora.com/about/privacy).

### **Contact Us**

Please contact our DataProtection Officer at [\[email protected\]](https://poe.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) if you have questions about this Privacy Policy. For more information about our privacy and data protection practices, including how to exercise your privacy rights, please visit the [Quora Privacy Policy](https://www.quora.com/about/privacy).

Company

Policy

Resources

Social

©️Copyright

2024

Quora Inc.

Company

Policy

Resources

Social

©️Copyright

2024

Quora Inc.

Company

Policy

Resources

Social

©️Copyright

2024

Quora Inc.
